{
    "subject": "Germaine_of_Foix",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ferdinand_II_of_Aragon",
    "human_readable": "Germaine of Foix is married to Ferdinand II of Aragon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9837592840194702,
            "question": "Are there any historical accounts about the marriage of Ferdinand II of Aragon and Germaine of Foix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9710965752601624,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Ferdinand II of Aragon and Germaine of Foix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417283535003662,
            "question": "To whom was Germaine of Foix married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.895625650882721,
            "question": "Who was married to Ferdinand II of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7620468139648438,
            "question": "What was the name of Ferdinand II of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7120338678359985,
            "question": "What era did Ferdinand II of Aragon and Germaine of Foix live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7067469358444214,
            "question": "What was the name of the queen who married Ferdinand II of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6999881863594055,
            "question": "Who is Ferdinand II of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4109870493412018,
            "question": "Who were some important people in Ferdinand II of Aragon's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3867041766643524,
            "question": "Is Germaine of Foix related to a Spanish king?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Germaine of Foix is married to Ferdinand II of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_25067_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some important people in Ferdinand II of Aragon's life?",
            "html": "yago_25067_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Ferdinand II of Aragon?",
            "html": "yago_25067_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the queen who married Ferdinand II of Aragon?",
            "html": "yago_25067_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25067_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text explicitly states that Germaine of Foix was the second wife of Ferdinand II of Aragon. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Germaine of Foix is married to Ferdinand II of Aragon. The documents explicitly state that Germaine was married to Ferdinand II, King of Aragon, and that she became Queen Consort of Aragon by virtue of this marriage (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25067/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Germaine of Foix was the second wife of Ferdinand II, King of Aragon\" and \"In May of 1509 Germaine gave birth to Ferdinand\u2019s son, John, who died shortly afterwards.\" This confirms her marriage to Ferdinand II of Aragon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}